

PROFILE

Young, self-reliant backend developer interested in taking the next step on the career path. So far I mainly worked with languages based on JVM (mostly Java but also Groovy and Kotlin) combined with Spring boot. Recently I became an enthusiast of hexagonal architecture. In my current job I was mostly responsible for the backend of projects that I worked on, but as part of development and maintenance of internal application, I worked also as frontend developer (Angular). Considering that, I'm open to work as fullstack developer. I'm a very organized person with a high level of focus. I enjoy sinking into big tasks, and successfully resolving those. For example as a member of a development team I had the opportunity to create a library implementing inbox pattern for other microservices in a project. When it comes to the code review process, I do it thoughtfully and carefully. In my opinion it's a key element when it comes to guaranteeing consistency with arrangements (especially when it comes to, for example, CQRS usage) and cohesion with business requirements. As a young developer I eagerly absorb knowledge and value people willing to share their experiences and good practices taught on their career path. Personally I'm hoping to become a valued element of the organized team and a support to less experienced developers.

HOBBY

- Football,
- Long walks with dog,
- PC hardware,
- Fantasy (mainly cyberpunk)

CONTACT

PHONE: 699-176-177

E-MAIL: bkucharczyk2000@gmail.com

Bartłomiej Kucharczyk

WORK EXPERIENCE

Envelo

09.08.2021 – 31.10.2021 Envelo Academy (Internship)
01.11.2021 – 31.10.2023 Junior Developer

01.11.2023 – currently Mid Developer

Description:

- Software development,
- Creating unit and integration tests,
- Self-reliant maintenance and development of internal application created as part of internship

EDUCATION

Warsaw University of Life Sciences
Degree - Computer Science, Engineer

01.10.2019 - 01.05.2023

Grade: 5.0

Rector scholarship for GPA.

SKILLS

Programming languages:

•	Java	☆ ☆ ☆ ☆ ☆
•	Groovy	\$ \$ \$ \$
•	Kotlin	☆ ☆ ☆
•	Typescript	☆ ☆ ☆

Frameworks:

•	Spring boot	* * * * *
•	Quarkus	☆ ☆ ☆
•	Angular	☆ ☆ ☆

Technologies:

	09.03.	
•	Docker	
•	PostgreSQL	* * * * *
•	Liquibase	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$
•	Redis	☆ ☆ ☆
•	Kafka	☆☆
•	Spock	☆ ☆ ☆ ☆
•	lunit	\$ \$ \$ \$ \$

Other

•	JUIIII	www
er:		
•	Git	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$
•	Maven	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$
•	Hexagonal architecture	$\Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond \Diamond$
•	CQRS	
•	DDD	☆☆☆
•	English language	B2